https://mybikinibrazil.com/terms-conditions/

Terms & Conditions - My Bikini Brazil
Oops! It appears that you have disabled your Javascript. In order for you to see this page as it is meant to appear, we ask that you please re-enable your Javascript!
Beautiful Brazilian Crochet Bikini
Shop
Crochet Bikinis
Crochet Thong Bikinis
Crochet Monokinis
Featured Best Sellers
Sizing Charts
Blog
Cookies
Like most interactive web sites this Company’s website [or ISP] uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies.
Links to this website
You may not create a link to any page of this website without our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.
Links from this website
We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.
Copyright Notice
Copyright and other relevant intellectual property rights exists on all text relating to the Company’s services and the full content of this website.
Communication
We have several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These, & other contact information, can be found on our Contact Us link on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s stated telephone, facsimile or mobile telephone numbers.
This company is located at 9404 Crescent Loop Circle, Tampa, Florida, 33619, USA or CX Postal 46, Garopaba, Santa Catarina, Brasil 88495-000.
General
The laws of United States govern these terms and conditions. By accessing this website you consent to these terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the United States of America in all disputes arising out of such access. If any of these terms are deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be severed from these terms and the remaining terms will continue to apply. Failure of the Company to enforce any of the provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each and every provision. These Terms and Conditions shall not be amended, modified, varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly authorised representatives of My Bikini Brazil.
Notification of Changes
My Bikini Brazil reserves the right to change these conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to our privacy policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and on other key pages on our site. If there are any changes in how we use our site customers’ Personally Identifiable Information, notification by e-mail or postal mail will be made to those affected by this change. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basis
These terms and conditions form part of the Agreement between the Client and ourselves. Your accessing of this website and/or undertaking of a booking or Agreement indicates your understanding, agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and Conditions contained herein. Your statutory Consumer Rights are unaffected.
Easy Returns
We are sorry things didn’t work out for you, but No Fear, My Bikini Brazil is Here, with a partial return, easy exchange process for all our products!
If you are unsatisfied with your product for any reason, you can return it for a partial refund minus a $44.95 restocking fee for each product, or exchange for any US In Stock product of similar value.
Return Details
• Must be within first 7 days of received merchandise.
• All merchandise must have tags still attached, not worn, and in good condition.
• Return shipping costs are not included on returns.
• You must email or call us first, with your intent to return or exchange your package.
Please send Returns and/or Exchanges to
My Bikini Brazil
9404 Crescent Loop Circle, Unit 108
Tampa, Florida,
33619
We will not respond to, exchange, or return, any Return/Exchange inquiry after 7 days of receipt of package, according to online tracking information.
Easy Exchanges
We are sorry things didn’t work out for you, but No Fear, My Bikini Brazil is Here, with a partial return, easy exchange process for all our products!
If you are unsatisfied with your product for any reason, you can return it for a partial refund minus a $44.95 restocking fee for each product, or exchange for any US In Stock product of similar value.
Return Details
• Must be within first 7 days of received merchandise.
• All merchandise must have tags still attached, not worn, and in good condition.
• Return shipping costs are not included on returns.
• You must email or call us first, with your intent to return or exchange your package.
Please send Returns and/or Exchanges to
My Bikini Brazil
9404 Crescent Loop Circle, Unit 108
Tampa, Florida,
33619
We will not respond to, exchange, or return, any Return/Exchange inquiry after 7 days of receipt of package, according to online tracking information.
Once we receive your Exchange Product we will begin processing your request for a new In Stock product of the same, or lessor value. Exchanges normally ship out within 72 business hours. We do not charge for shipping on exchanged products. We do not except two time exchanges/ returns. Thus, if you are unhappy with your exchanged product, we will not accept a second time return and/or exchange.
What is Processing Time?
Once the order is placed, we gather the products and package them. The average processing time is 3 days, but it varies by product and the stock status. For some products or for larger-quantity orders, the processing time may be up to 5 – 10 business days.
Privacy Statement
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information collected from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers. Our government has created specific offences for unauthorised actions against computer systems and data. We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible.
Returns & Exchanges
We are sorry things didn’t work out for you, but No Fear, My Bikini Brazil is Here, with a partial return, easy exchange process for all our products!
If you are unsatisfied with your product for any reason, you can return it for a partial refund minus a $44.95 restocking fee for each product, or exchange for any US In Stock product of similar value.
Return Details
• Must be within first 7 days of received merchandise.
• All merchandise must have tags still attached, not worn, and in good condition.
• Return shipping costs are not included on returns.
• You must email or call us first, with your intent to return or exchange your package.
Please send Returns and/or Exchanges to
My Bikini Brazil
9404 Crescent Loop Circle, Unit 108
Tampa, Florida,
33619
We will not respond to, exchange, or return, any Return/Exchange inquiry after 7 days of receipt of package, according to online tracking information.
Once we receive your Exchange Product we will begin processing your request for a new In Stock product of the same, or lessor value. Exchanges normally ship out within 72 business hours. We do not charge for shipping on exchanged products. We do not except two time exchanges/ returns. Thus, if you are unhappy with your exchanged product, we will not accept a second time return and/or exchange.
Confidentiality
We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and as such, any information concerning the Client and their respective Client Records may be passed to third parties. However, Client records are regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, other than [our manufacturer/supplier(s) and] if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities. Clients have the right to request sight of, and copies of any and all Client Records we keep, on the proviso that we are given reasonable notice of such a request. Clients are requested to retain copies of any literature issued in relation to the provision of our services. Where appropriate, we shall issue Client’s with appropriate written information, handouts or copies of records as part of an agreed contract, for the benefit of both parties.
We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.
Shipping & Delivery
Free Standard Shipping on US and International Orders Over $99.00.
My Bikini Brazil ships worldwide. Orders normally ship out within 24 to 72 business hours. You should receive your order anywhere from 5-9 business days from the date that it is shipped out, not necessarily from the date that it is placed. After your payment is authorized and verified, it can still take up to 72 business hours to process your order. This is just an estimate, though, and doesn’t include weekends or holidays. Shipping addresses in Hawaii, Alaska, APO/FPO, PO Boxes and US Territories will be shipped via USPS Priority Mail. You will receive a shipping notification email that will notify you of the carrier we’ve used to ship your order, and the different tracking options available for it.
Shipping Rates & Delivery
Service
Cost
Delivery Time
Standard US & International Shipping
$14.00
14-20 Business Days
Priority US & International Shipping
$22.00
7-14 Business Days
Express US & International Shipping
$49.00
3-7 Business Days
Overnight Shipping is not available at this time.
Hawaii, Alaska, PO Boxes, APO/FPO & U.S Territories
We accept orders shipped to PO boxes and APO/FPO or U.S. territories.  Orders shipped to these addresses must be sent via USPS Priority Mail service.
Exclusions and Limitations
Exclusions and Limitations
The information on this web site is provided on an “as is” basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, My Bikini Brazil.
excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature; and
excludes all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this Company of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.
My Bikini Brazil does not however exclude liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are affected.
Payments
My Bikini Brazil accepts all major Credit/Debit Cards and Debit Card transfers. All goods remain the property of the Company until paid for in full.
Cancellation Policy
Minimum 24 hours notice of cancellation required. Notification for instance, in person, via email, mobile phone ‘text message’ and/or fax, or any other means will be accepted subject to confirmation in writing. We reserve the right to levy a $25 charge to cover any subsequent administrative expenses.
Termination of Agreements
Both the Client and ourselves have the right to terminate any Services Agreement for any reason, including the ending of services that are already underway. No refunds shall be offered, where a Service is deemed to have begun and is, for all intents and purposes, underway. Any monies that have been paid to us which constitute payment in respect of the provision of unused Services, shall be refunded.
Availability
Unless otherwise stated, the products featured on this website are only available worldwide. Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means, without the express written consent of the Company. The Company does not warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.
My Bikini Brazil My Bikini Brazil was founded in 2002 with the main goal to bring Brazilian High Fashion, and superior Crochet Swimwear to the US, Canada, Europe, and Oceania. My Bikini Brazil`s superior original handmade products and personal customer service casts them far above the competition with a quality level crochet swimwear collection that is absolutely superb in its elegance and longevity.
Find Us On
Information
Affiliate Platform with a $25 Sign Up Bonus
Beautiful Brazilian Crochet Bikini
Blog
Cart
Checkout
Contact Us
SUBSCRIBE FOR COUPONS!
